# PATRICK THOMAS WELLMAN

PatrickThomasWellman.com

GitHub.comPatrickWellman

#### **SUMMARY**

Patrick specializes in building and deploying design focused mobile- responsive web applications. He has a well trained eye for aesthetically pleasing layouts and themes helping to improve overall user experience. He possesses a strong knowledge of HTML5, advanced CSS3 and SASS. Patrick works with JavaScript and React to build reusable components for web applications. He is extremely well versed in Word Press as well. Patrick is able to work with clients to design theme based and completely custom websites. He has also assisted with establishing online presence for his clients.

#### **MAIN TECHNOLOGIES**

React React Router HTML5 CSS3 FlexBox SASS SASSY CSS CSS Grid JavaScript GitHub Responsive UI Adobe Photoshop Adobe Lightroom Color.Adobe VS Code Semantic UI

### **EXPERIENCE**

## The Presidential Parlour, Front End Developer, 2020-Current

Designed, built, and deployed company's mobile responsive website using Word Press and the Divi builder as well as SEO management. Linked website to booking service. Created reusable components that are implemented in different areas of the site. Responsible for setting up the business on Google Maps, Apple Maps, Google My Business, Mail Chimp and custom emails. Continues to maintain site and update as needed.

## Roventures, Web Developer, 2019-Current

Patrick assisted in the development and proof of concepts for the rebuild of the video streaming platform. He focused on design, responsive layout, and implementing new libraries.

**The Thompson Hotel**, Pastry Chef, January 2017-2019 **The Catbird Seat Restaurant**, Executive Pastry Chef, June 2017-January 2018 **Meat Market Restaurants**, Corporate Pastry Chef, June 2016 - June 2017

Working as a Pastry Chef, Patrick has been in charge of remotely strategizing logistics, staffing, and delegating tasks for events in excess of 3000 people all while managing several departments of up to 40 people spread across a large territories. He has demonstrated excellent time management and communication skills, as well the ability to remain calm under pressure.

#### **EDUCATION**

Florida State University School of Business

#### **Online Resources**

Udemy: Modern React with Redux 2020, The Modern Javascript Bootcamp 2020, Advanced CSS and SASS, Build Responsive websites with HTML5 and CSS3, Code Academy, React & AWS Docs, YouTube, GitHub, StackOverFlow, Meetup, Hacker News, Code Newbie

## **REFERENCES**

Rohan Damani, Lead Developer, Disney (864) 497-7223 Chef Zak Miller, Chef Instructor at The CIA - (917) 742-2122 Chef Kelly Fields, Corporate Pastry The Besh Group - (415) 699-4236